{
    "questions": [  
    {
        "question": "1+1 = ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
        "1","2","3","4"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "2+2 = ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
        "4","3","2","1"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "2+1 = ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
        "1","2","3","4"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "4+2 = ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
        "5","6","3","4"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "5+5 = ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
        "7","8","9","10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "7+2 = ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
        "7","8","9","10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "9+4 = ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
        "10","12","13","14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "3+5 = ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
        "7","8","9","10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "12+2 = ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
        "10","12","13","14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "2*4 = ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
        "7","8","9","10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "22*7 = ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
        "1","2","3","154"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "300+22 = ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
        "121","223","322","442"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "17+54 = ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
        "81","62","71","45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "1+1-1+1+1+1-1+1+1*1-1-1*1+1+1+1-1 = ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
        "3","4","5","6"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "2*2*2+2 = ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
        "12","32","16","10"
        ]
    }
    
    
    ]
}